也就是所谓的混沌反应。
what's called a chaotic response,
我们会感到沮丧、绝望、
which looks like depression, despair,
有种停摆了的感觉。
kind of a shutting down.
在容忍范围的另一边 则是一种更僵化的反应：
And on the other side of this window is a more rigid response:
否认，
denial,
愤怒，
anger,
僵化。
rigid.
所以当这种情况发生时，
And so when that happens,
我们实际上失去了情绪整合、
we actually lose our capacity to be integrated,
韧性、适应力，
resilient, adaptive,
以及所有我们想要的情绪控制力。
all those things that we want to be.
这很正常，
And this is totally normal,
但也在全世界发生着，不是吗？
but it's happening all around the world right now, right?
我们都在这些不同的感受 和情绪之间摇摆不定。
We're all vacillating between these different feelings and emotions.